Plaintiff Kaya
In my hometown before marriage
I have already had a child
Huh...
this…
What does this mean?
uh?
uh? Oh, no, right?
Plaintiff hid the fact of childbirth
deceive the defendant
It was a fraudulent marriage.
Why didn't you tell me?
‘I have given birth before marriage’
Kaya, is that really true?
now completely
It's a new situation.
Annulment of marriage is different from divorce.
The marriage itself is completely invalidated.
I never got married in the first place
It will work
I came to Korea on a marriage visa.
It's all canceled
I'm being kicked out of this country.
Mr. Kaya!
yes?
under…
It's a mountain beyond the mountain
I thought I finally revealed the truth
Cancellation of marriage?
Raped my daughter-in-law
Are you going to call off the marriage?
This can be solved by law
It's not a case
- Your fists must be stronger than the law!
- Oh, hey, hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa
There's nothing to get upset about
what we do
- In the end, it's someone else's business.
- Yes?
Hey, are you saying that now?
Then can we go in?
- Come in…
- Attorney Park!
yes?
Group health checkup this week
You didn't forget, right?
Oh, you're new
Oh, Attorney Kang too.
Don't miss out this time
Is Attorney Jang not there?
- Oh, give it to me.
- Ah
we are now
I don't have time for that...
According to company regulations
All employees receive it.
Because there is also an endoscopy
Fast from the evening before.
eww…
What is the most leisurely team?
Wait a minute, what did you just say!
Good luck
They say there’s nothing to get upset about.
Well, if you want it, you can take it.
Now, because of Attorney Kang.
Do you know that it gets hotter?
Then let it cool down.
Argh!
under! under…
- I haven't done it yet.
- Ha…
Take a deep breath
Hold your breath
'6, 2, 8, 3, 5'
- What about this?
- '8, 3, 5, 2, 9'
- '5, 9, 6, 4, 2'
- This.
- '2, 9, 5, 7, 4'
- What about this?
- '3, 8, 2, 3, 7'
Look
You don't hear it
Anesthesia~
What's not working?
Ah, Park, Park Byun
Doesn’t Park Byun get an endoscopy?
Ugh!
we are
I've already finished the checkup
I returned to work
Only Attorney Kang
Because of all the fuss
You're late.
Ah, but earlier
It was really funny, ah
It was such a waste to see it alone, really.
What, what cow, what are you talking about?
What, what, what did I say?
Okay, that's it.
Get dressed quickly and come out
Come out
Yes?
what?
ah…
'Marriage is a sacred promise'
'A house built on sand
'As if it couldn't last forever'
‘A marriage concluded on lies, too’
‘It cannot last’
‘Judge Koo Ji-won’
Respectfully, your honor.
Your honor
As a judge specializing in domestic affairs
Working for 10 years
Faithfulness in marriage
Above all else, you emphasized
Marital history, presence of children, criminal record
whatever it is
If you trick your partner into getting married
mercilessly
A judgment was made to cancel the marriage.
I just ruled according to the law.
Yes, your honor.
This case is also legal
Please declare justice
Civil Act Article 816 No. 3
'By fraud or duress
'When the intention to marry is expressed'
Hiding the fact of childbirth
If it doesn't apply here
what is
Would this apply to you?
The plaintiff side
To reveal childbirth history
Would you respond to your physical feelings?
Sorry, your honor.
body feelings
no need
Uh, then…
Plaintiff before marriage
The fact that you have ever given birth
I will admit it
Ah! eww…
That damn bitch!
That bitch!
Is that true, plaintiff?
Mr. Kaya
Yes, your honor.
At first
She filed a complaint claiming that her husband strangled her.
Now again
Actually before marriage
Have you ever had a child?
The replacement manuscript means
Where and to what extent is the truth?
Sorry, your honor.
Without hiding the truth
I'll reveal it.
Plaintiff's own newspaper
Please allow me one more time
Thank you, your honor.
before marrying the defendant
Have you ever given birth to a baby?
yes
How old were you?
I was fourteen years old
How old was the other person?
I was thirty-two years old
Did you know each other?
This is someone I've never seen before.
It may be difficult, but
please tell me
What happened?
I am
When I was thirteen
firewood in the mountains
Picking it up
I was kidnapped by that man
Stop…
no!
It's a lie!
son! Son, Dongmin!
I'm sorry, your honor.
I would like to request a short break.
Are you having a hard time?
Lawyer
It's just the beginning
that terrible thing
As it was
I remember every detail
You need to say something.
It's really a trial
It's cruel
Mr. Kaya
You can do it, right?
You worked hard
thank you
Your honor
As you just heard
The plaintiff was only thirteen years old.
Kidnapped by a man from a neighboring village
At that man's house for a week
I was raped while incarcerated.
Because of the sexual assault
unwanted
I ended up giving birth
if necessary
the people of the plaintiff's hometown
I will apply as a witness.
I'm sorry
Ah, for now
I heard you well
You prepared hard
But
This is it
What do you need?
The defendant's agent
I just read the newspaper content
Didn't you hear anything?
The plaintiff was forced to…
Oh, so that's it
What does this have to do with this incident?
I have no blood or tears
I'm not that cold-blooded
You went through something like that at a young age.
How difficult must it have been?
I am
No matter what reason the plaintiff gave birth
About the fact of childbirth itself
What I want to do is take responsibility for that.
no
I just
Such an important fact
Why do you marry someone
Did you get married without talking about it?
I'm asking
Isn't that right?
Fraudulent used car dealer
Hiding unfavorable facts
Revealing only favorable facts
How is this different from selling a car?
Our defendant
You may have seen it before
Hide nothing…
I can't hide it
However, I taught myself Korean.
To be able to speak fluently
The smart manuscript
ahead of marriage
About this important fact
Not a single word
did not talk to the defendant
This is about the person you are marrying.
Is that God?
Then me too
I would like to ask the defendant's attorney.
yes
When I was young, I was walking down the street
Even getting bitten by a dog
Now to your wife
Did you say everything in advance?
what else is that
Is this a useless question?
What's the difference?
- yes?
- The manuscript is
It's literally a long road
I was bitten by a crazy dog.
Regardless of your will
I was the victim of one-sided violence.
What is essentially different?
Anyway, this...
Ah~
‘It’s different because it’s sexual violence’?
‘It’s different because it’s a sex-related issue’?
Then, let me ask you again.
The defendant's representative
happened before marriage
Partner in any sexual relationship
Date, location, and other details
Everything…
no, now
What are we going to do?
Plaintiff Representative
I understand what you want to say.
Please argue more seriously.
Did you pass it by?
Ah
Sorry if I overlooked it, your honor.
I just
The defendant is now
The logic that claims it is too obvious
I'm asking if it's really obvious.
Anyway
The facts of childbirth are different!
‘My partner has a child’
Is there anything more important than this?
The child immediately after birth
The perpetrator's parents immediately took him away.
Not even once since then
I've never met or seen
Still, the future
Isn't that something you don't know?
Moreover, at a young age
The fact that you gave birth
After pregnancy or childbirth
What impact might it have?
unknown
Childbirth history
ahead of marriage
must be notified to the other party
This is one of the most important facts
Isn’t this common sense?
Now the plaintiff's attorney
Desperately using all kinds of sophistry,
From this common sense
I'm trying to look away
Your honor
Also from the Supreme Prosecutors' Central Investigation Department
How do you defend yourself?
I admit it
That's common sense
It's important
Laws must also be based on common sense.
By the way
Sometimes
very sometimes
That common sense
There are things you miss
most people
What happened to Kaya
I live without experiencing it
At the young age of thirteen
Kidnapping, confinement, sexual assault
The pain and fear of these people
Common sense is easy to forget
To fill this gap, the Constitution
basic human rights
This is guaranteed
Article 17 of the Constitution
‘All citizens’
'Secrecy and freedom of private life
'Not infringed'
In the world
Things that force disclosure
so harsh
There are things like that too.
yes
The fact that you have a history of giving birth
Things you need to know about your marriage partner
It's true that it's an important fact.
That's common sense
But even that common sense
protected by the constitution
In front of basic human rights
The minimal exception is
Shouldn’t we admit it?
To victims of child sexual violence
To reveal to yourself what happened to you
Forcing
That's it!
Hey, is that what people do?
Your honor
This whole incident once
please take a look
What about this case?
Victims of child sexual violence
again after marriage
I was sexually assaulted by my father-in-law
can't last any longer
this marriage
This is a lawsuit asking for an end.
However, the perpetrator, the in-laws,
The in-laws didn't say a word of apology.
Rather, the plaintiff experienced
Because of child sexual violence
Denying this marriage itself
I'm trying to cancel
According to my common sense
This is called a red-light attack.
It's called dastardly revenge.
Your honor
Is my common sense correct?
Please check if the defendant’s common sense is correct.
Please judge wisely.
Your honor
I will also tell you one thing.
I am now
What the plaintiff experienced
To anyone I met on the street
I need to make it public
I'm not claiming
We have to live together for the rest of our lives
To the marriage partner
I should have talked about it
is claiming
But you hid it instead of talking about it?
Why?
To tell the truth
that the other person will not get married
Because I know it well
Unless this is a fraudulent marriage
What would it be?
Your honor
Plaintiff's attorney
Many flashy words
Although they are lined up
That's right
The essence does not change
Marriage is also a contract.
Contracts resulting from fraud
It is possible to cancel
Please declare your principles
Your honor
Thank you for your hard work
Lawyer Kang
Park Byun also had a hard time.
Thank you, lawyers.
Mr. Kaya
Now judge
As a stubborn principled person
He is a famous person
Because of childbirth history
Marriage annulment decision
I've already posted it
probably self-judgment
It won't be easy to change
It's okay though
Yes?
For the first time in my life
'Cause someone fought for me
Even in this far away country
For foreigners...
Thank you so much, lawyers.
Congratulations, Attorney Kang.
- Yes?
- I just became a public interest lawyer.
I think you've taken the first step.
What does that mean?
Going into a fight even though you know you will lose
That's public
Well…
Well, it's definitely not my style.
My car is this way.
I know
'2025 dedan674221'
'2025 dedan674519'
I will pronounce judgment.
Article 816 of the Civil Code
No. 3 is
One side of the couple
Due to fraud or duress
When the intention to marry is expressed
Annulment of marriage by court
I can claim it
It is stipulated
The important promise of marriage
The people ahead
lies to each other
It shouldn't exist
Even more so
I had a child before marriage
This is in marriage
can have a big impact
It's an important fact
Of course
Duty to notify the other party
I'll say there is
‘just’, ‘just’
Just
Even the law sometimes
There are times when you need to make an exception.
Plaintiff has ever given birth
Although it is true
This is regardless of your will.
For child sexual assault crimes
You have been harmed
Relationship with the child born
It's already been disconnected for a long time
To the plaintiff who is a victim of a crime
Obligation to notify this yourself
Erasing is
It's too harsh
can't help but see
Therefore
Plaintiff gave birth
What was not notified
In light of the duty of good faith
Because it cannot be considered worthy of criticism,
The ruling is as follows:
order
by this office
Plaintiff and defendant divorce
Defendant's counterclaim is dismissed.
Plaintiff won
This is ridiculous!
This is a scam, a scam!
This doesn't make sense
- Thank you, Judge.
- Bitch!
Let go! Right side!
We won!
Can I live in Korea?
- really?
- yes yes!
Thank you, lawyer.
Hmm?
Wow
As a cheap emotional sell
Shake up court order
Don't do that, you'll be disgraced
Huh? Did you fall?
Shut up
Wow
See you soon
Yes~
Should I appeal?
Well, you'll figure it out.
Rather, Park Byun
- Huh?
- I won the case.
I'll shoot
- Now?
-Are you not hungry?
her…
what?
Um~
The burger is so delicious
The view here is also very good
But what happened today?
We have something to talk about
The trial is over
Attorney Gippeum Park
재밌는 사람이더라?
Attorney Park? why?
You were threatening me?
Do you have a video of your brother?
I heard you saw the video?
yes
Ha…
Who sent it?
There was no caller
Of course, Attorney Kang
공격하고 싶은 사람이겠죠
Of course it's a conspiracy.
I do that
Do you look like someone who would take a bribe?
That's right
I'm not the type of person to take it that openly.
clumsily
Sure! So how do I...
Wait a minute
Well then, what
As someone who will receive it
Are you saying you can see it?
I don't understand
I rewatched it several times
- After…
- No matter how you look at it
강 변호사님 맞아요
There are no signs of manipulation
I'm disappointed, Attorney Park.
Disappointment?
Yeah, that's an unclear video.
I saw one
So suddenly me
Are you treated like a criminal?
under…
Don’t you know the presumption of innocence?
You speak so easily.
What is it?
That's enough if you think about it that way
Isn't this a suspicious situation?
What is it?
동영상만 갖고 얘기하는 거
- No.
- Then what is it!
About public interest cases
Even though I have no interest at all
one day suddenly
I quit my job as a successful judge.
Transformed into public defense?
Don't you think it's strange?
With someone else's good intentions
So carelessly
I'm not misinterpreting it.
How far can I go
my experience and my abilities
사회적 약자를 위해 가지고…
70% win rate
I heard you bet as a condition of the deal.
Oh my
Didn't you know?
I heard you bet a 70% chance of winning?
instead next year
Would you like me to recommend you as a candidate for Supreme Court Justice?
If you don't keep that condition
We will dismantle it.
Pro Bono Team
Ha…
I didn't know
We are Attorney Kang
For the stakes on the Supreme Court Justice bet
I was working hard
About that
how far can i go
It means that I will do my best...
Before
I still want to believe it though
Attorney Kang is a good person.
Yes?
When arguing in court
It seems sincere.
But other team members
When everyone knows
Even then, Attorney Kang
I don't know if everyone will believe it
Even just Nanhee
Why did Attorney Kang come from the beginning…
Why should I care?
- yes?
- Think what you want.
I don't want others to think about me
What do you think?
I'm not interested in that.
No matter what I feel inside
Wouldn’t it be okay if you win?
Is a 20% win rate fun? great?
Hey, maybe
Losing is not my hobby.
teamwork today
Because I think I've chopped it enough
I'll wake up first
Because I'll calculate what's mine
Don't worry
Ah...
hello!
What, why is the winning team’s mood like this?
- uh?
- why?
I submitted an appeal.
Attorney Myeong-Hoon Woo
Really?
Wow, what is it?
Are you a fiery man who never gives up?
It's because I'm so obsessed
Usually, second place people are like that.
This time again
What kind of argument are you trying to make?
- Is it okay?
Already an impressive frame
It's a planned case
Now
Look
How do I turn this around?
It's a foolish beggar
I guess so, right?
Well, there is Attorney Kang.
Well, what are you worried about?
Then~
- Unlucky.
- Now
Look
manuscript
After being kidnapped
at the man's house
How long did you stay?
About nine months
Ah…
It's been almost a year?
over that long period of time
It's like a room locked with a lock.
Were you trapped?
- No.
- Really?
Then why didn't you run away?
Oh, maybe
Was that man nice to you?
So much so that I don’t even think about my mom?
Your honor
defendant agent
Please be careful with your expressions
Yes, I will be careful.
Plaintiff, I will ask you again.
Why didn't you run away?
ran away
A week after being caught
Oh, then it was like that.
to the man's house
So you're back again?
Came back voluntarily?
Because I want to
I'm not going back!
my baby
How scared were you, my baby?
mom, mom
Go back!
Dad
You have already lost your value as a woman.
You know, right?
who will take you
I can't help it
When that man comes to get you
Just follow along and live in that town.
- Honey!
- You be quiet!
go back
Mom, save me
Mom, I don't want to go
I'm scared
The plaintiff's parents
You sent it back again.
‘Follow and live in that village’
So you haven't given permission to get married?
Right?
marriage?
The lawyer said that
Do you call it marriage?
Isn't it? with parental permission
We lived together at my in-laws’ house…
That man!
They hit me every day
Every night...
I got hit
I was only thirteen years old
Lawyer
Still
If we lived together for nine months
It's just a somewhat stable relationship.
Can't you see it?
I ran away again
in nine months
Uh, then what about childbirth?
in that house
Didn't you give birth to a child?
yes!
me
In that hellish place
I can't live any more
I ran away and went home
while pregnant
Then at Kaya’s house.
Are you having a child?
no
Why?
Dad, Mom
Please open the door, please
Baby… my baby
mom
Is my daughter okay?
honey
- Go back now!
- Dad
why do i say
I didn't listen and came back on my own.
With a body like that
cheating
Go back quickly
daughter, my daughter
mom
Dad, Mom
my father
I couldn't come home
I
with help from people
There…
I gave birth to a child
um
I see.
Okay
Thank you for your hard work, manuscript.
That's it.
I will pronounce judgment.
Appeal in this case
According to the results of the hearing
Plaintiff has been kidnapped and sexually assaulted in the past
It's true that it happened
Afterwards, I stayed with the man for about 9 months.
The fact of cohabitation is acknowledged
- ‘just’, ‘just’
- 'just'
Besides
In light of the plaintiff's date of birth,
Not the first kidnapping and sexual violence
After that, with the permission of the plaintiff's parents,
with the man in question
When we were living together
It appears that pregnancy has occurred
No way…
Considering these circumstances,
Plaintiff's pregnancy and childbirth
Plaintiff's honor
This is a seriously damaging fact.
It's hard to see
This is ridiculous!
- Inspector
- Oh, yeah.
Let’s sit down first.
I will continue
If so, please notify us of this fact
By imposing an obligation
The confidentiality and freedom of the plaintiff's private life
It's seriously infringing
It's hard to see
Plaintiff has a history of giving birth
Actions that were not notified
It is a ground for cancellation of marriage.
Therefore, we rule as follows:
The first trial ruling, which came to a different conclusion,
Destroy this
between plaintiff and defendant
March 13, 2023
Reported to the general mayor
cancel the marriage
Plaintiff to defendant
Pay 10 million won in alimony.
Your honor!
Ouch!
- thank you!
- That's it.
Hahahaha!
That…
What does that mean, lawyer?
huh?
Did we lose?
Mr. Kaya…
Ugh, tsk.
‘Because my father gave permission’
‘It’s not sexual violence’?
This is it, it's a fart!
Argh!
No, why are you taking mine…
Ah, Mr.
Ah! No, that doesn't make sense!
No, how…
uh? Wait a minute
Kaya's father-in-law
You're the county mayor for maintaining the region, right?
Who is the member of the National Assembly in that district?
Lee Doo-cheol
Rep. Lee Doo-cheol
But I used to be a prosecutor.
3rd term congressman?
Crazy, this guy!
Byeol is the father of the accuser during the incident!
Judge Kang, that person
He just called me threatening.
what are you
Are you saying there was animal abuse or something?
Wow, creepy!
External pressure?
Connection? that…
If it's for that reason
It would be better
What does that mean?
While listening to the reason for the ruling earlier,
Did you get goosebumps?
‘Ah, this person is legally
You are convinced that this is right.'
'I got pregnant again after sexual violence.'
'그럼 고지했어야지'
Like solving some kind of math problem
That peaceful expression...
under…
No, well, that damn legal principle, whatever.
What kind of monster is this?
The law is for people
Doesn't it exist?
The law is not a monster
Treat it like solving a math problem
The indifference of the judges is monstrous.
Let's go
supreme court
Mr. Kaya
It's really amazing
I found a used sewing machine for you.
inside the shelter
It's almost like a fashion show.
cute
- Are you okay?
- Yes
President Choi Young-seop
Historic UN plenary session speech
Two months to go
On World Refugee Day
This speech is
Following economically and culturally advanced countries,
Established as an advanced country in human rights
Korea’s status
To announce to the whole world
- I'm looking forward to it.
- Ms. Kaya
Are you okay?
yes
I'm fine
Lawyers have a harder time
Oh no, no
Although we lost in the second trial,
In the Supreme Court...
I'm not worried
I believe it
You believe it?
hmm…
Wrong things happen everywhere.
But Korea is amazing
In the end, we all do it right.
If the president does something wrong, kick him out.
My father-in-law is also a powerful man, but
They arrested me right away.
i believe
Our trial too
I'm sure everything will work out.
yes
I will definitely make it happen, Kaya.
Father-in-law takes care of his daughter-in-law
It also came from far away
Daughter-in-law in a lonely situation
This case of sexual assault
sexual assault crime
Special Act on Punishment, etc.
Pursuant to Article 5, Paragraph 1
Sentenced to imprisonment for more than 7 years
As a serious crime that must be punished
Strictly
It's a case that requires accountability.
I can't help but do it.
Because of this, the victim
how much pain you must be going through
This court dares to
It's not even easy to fathom
'therefore', 'accordingly'
- 'Accordingly'
- Just
- Huh?
- The defendant is elderly.
Hundreds of local residents
leniency to the defendant
I am pleading
Besides
The defendant
He is a first time offender with no criminal record.
This doesn't make sense
No way, I want to get a reprieve
Is it build up?
Hey, the statutory sentence is more than 7 years.
Even if the salary is reduced once, it is 3 years and 6 years.
Up to 3 years in prison
You can get probation.
It is impossible to collect milk
Meanwhile, the victim's usual clothes
Regarding conduct, etc.
Statements from residents criticizing
There was some
Recent victim's premarital birth and
on the grounds of deception
The decision to cancel the marriage was made
In light of
These statements
I can't take it lightly
At the time of this incident, the defendant
drunk
Inability to discern things
ability to make decisions
It is acknowledged that it was weak.
First of all, 1st lane
Reduce mental and physical weakness
2 lanes
Taking into account the various summits seen earlier,
Within the range of the reduced sentence
The ruling is as follows:
Two reductions?
no way…
the defendant
Sentenced to 3 years in prison
However, for 5 years from the date of confirmation of this judgment
The execution of the above sentence is suspended.
Oh no!
Please be quiet
To the defendant
To hold them accountable
200 hours of community service
Attending sexual violence treatment lectures
I order 80 hours
more than
Judgment is concluded
yes, all
Please stand up.
Thank you, lawyer.
But
Well, community service, that thing.
Isn't it too long?
Oh my, governor
Always serving
Haven't you lived?
Just do a little more, okay?
yes
- Good luck!
- Yes, please come in.
yes
for a long time
While sitting on the law school
I forgot
Feelings under law school
This feeling of despair
Huh?
why?
Well, what else is going on?
It was dismissed, Ms. Kaya’s appeal.
- Huh?
- uh?
Does that make sense?
How long has it been since you appealed?
Look, look
How so fast?
Is it the final decision?
Ah, this is enough
As soon as the reasons for appeal are filed
They dismissed it right away?
Who is the presiding judge?
This is Supreme Court Justice Shin Jung-seok.
Justice Shin Jung-seok?
Lawyer Kang
When the Central District Court was there
Aren't you the chief judge?
After graduating from high school
Almost like an orphan
A bastard like you who has no roots
Me, who believed in me and pulled me in
Are you betraying me like this?
You viper-like bastard!
If the appeal is dismissed,
The judgment to cancel the marriage is confirmed.
Kaya's marriage visa was also canceled.
It's called deportation.
What should I do…
Lawyer Kang
Kang, lawyer Kang?
Kang, Lawyer Kang!
Oh, where are you going?
For the first time in my life
'Cause someone fought for me
Even in this far away country
For foreigners...
Celebrating this World Refugee Day
In a speech at the UN plenary session
I focus on economy and culture.
Even in the field of human rights
Our Republic of Korea
Proud to lead the world...
They are laughing
“O&Partners”
Attorney Park
Ah, what time is it already…
Why are you going to work now?
yes?
I will soon submit it to the Ministry of Justice.
Draft application for postponement of deportation
I wrote it all down
What about other team members?
Other team members are in the data room
Materials related to the Immigration Control Act
I'm looking through everything.
- Did you sleep well?
- Are you here?
What about Jang Byun?
Attorney Jang
You're at the Ministry of Justice's immigration office.
Lawyer Kang ran away.
Run away, run away!
Are you going to give up like this?
I have to find some way
Who gives up?
Well, how much did you prepare?
Let's get started
If the marriage annulment decision is confirmed,
Ministry of Justice, Immigration Service, and Foreigners’ Office
Immediate residency status
They said they would notify me of cancellation?
Now from here, really now
Isn’t it a race against time?
That's right
Article 46, Paragraph 1 of the Immigration Control Act
It becomes a source of forced eviction...
Tskcha
Take a look at this
Lawyer
Please check this out
No, that doesn't mean
You can't win unconditionally
Article 23 of the Administrative Procedure Act
There is an application for suspension of execution.
Litigation to cancel forced eviction order
If we do it together
You say you can buy time?
Ah, but there is a problem
The current Immigration Control Act is
Necessary enforcement suspension provisions
I don't leave it there
Don't just trust the legal process
A public opinion campaign must be held simultaneously.
Well then, there is only one conclusion.
First, a lawsuit to cancel the forced eviction order
raised immediately
Second, parallel application for suspension of execution
Third, the court has no choice but to decide
for humanitarian reasons
Are you highlighting...
The documents are due tonight
You need to prepare
Once a protection order is issued, within a short period of time
you will be repatriated
Ah…
uh…
How did it go?
Smoke, smoke, smoke, right?
Dismissed?
Then this time
Let’s post it on a national petition.
Inform the media as well
It's no use
I'm expelling you tomorrow.
With illegal immigrants
Yes? What?
ah…
no
No, what is this?
No, does this make sense?
The father-in-law who sexually assaulted
Release it
The victim is deported...
What kind of country is this?
Now, stand here.
one, two
- Hey, me.
- Yes
G, g, home now...
- Oh, yes, I understand.
- Hey there.
line, teacher
I haven't received the money for my work yet.
- I need to get that.
- Yes, yes, I understand.
Now, I'll stand in front.
Now, stand in line.
You can follow me in.
Come on in.
Now, we won't talk
Come to work, come to work
Now, slowly, slowly
Wait a minute!
Lawyer
This is Kaya's lawyer.
Please release Ms. Kaya immediately.
I formally request
This person's visa was canceled
Is this a forced deportation?
We are
persecuted in this land
On behalf of Kaya
What kind of country is this?
under…
Let's go into exile
Yes? What?
Let's go into exile.
In this country right now!
Asylum?
Lawyer
According to Article 5, Paragraph 6 of the Refugee Act,
Refugee applicants
Decisions on whether to recognize refugees
until confirmed
You can stay in Korea
Please release Kaya.
Right now
Now, please be quiet.
- Plaintiff's representative
- Yes
What are we going to do now?
Is the trial a joke?
It's a joke
I am now
File a lawsuit to cancel refugee status non-recognition
I'm just doing it
I would like to ask the Defendant, the Director of the Immigration Office,
Here is the plaintiff Kaya
to be recognized as a refugee
I officially applied
Because I was rejected
Cancellation suit for this
I'm just doing it
No, I mean
Why is the manuscript
Are you a refugee?
The manuscript is already
I got married internationally 2 years ago.
Isn’t this someone who came to Korea?
Your honor
What has the plaintiff been through so far?
You know.
From father-in-law's sexual violence
marriage annulment lawsuit
Even forced deportation.
That's applying for refugee status
Who cares?
According to Supreme Court precedent
Persecution is a requirement for refugee status
life, body or
including threats to freedom
About the essential dignity of human beings
serious infringement or discrimination
refers to an act that causes
Unless what the plaintiff suffered was persecution
What on earth is persecution?
Let's say yes.
Then why on earth
Applying for refugee status incorrectly!
Damn, exile?
Uh, where?
What, America, America? france?
Why apply for refugee status
Do you mean to do it in Korea?
I heard you were persecuted in Korea.
Then of course
Applying for refugee status in a third country
Applying for asylum is common sense.
Why in Korea
Are you asking for asylum?
That's really
Is this Korea?
What?
Your honor, I am
To the judiciary of the Republic of Korea
I'm asking a question.
Free the perpetrator of sexual violence
A country where victims are forcibly deported
Hiding the fact of child sexual abuse
A country that treats marriage fraudsters
Such a country
Is this really Korea?
Following economically advanced countries and culturally advanced countries,
Now we are a human rights advanced country
A country proud of the world
I know
Korea is that kind of country.
Surely the judge
The dignity of the plaintiff was brutally trampled upon.
Such a barbaric country
It's Korea
Are you acknowledging this?
Your honor
Now the plaintiff's attorney
Nonsense sophistry
It's lined up
If this isn't Korea right now
What country is it?
Then the defendant's agent likes
Let me explain with legal logic.
According to the Constitution of the Republic of Korea
The territory of the Republic of Korea is
Korean Peninsula and
This is the entire accompanying book.
Just north of the ceasefire line
Legally an anti-state organization
The North Korean government
effectively
I'm just in control
Like this
Even within the territory of the Republic of Korea
Other countries may exist
Victims turn away
A country that is only lenient on perpetrators
Ignoring the powerless
A country that protects powerful people
perpetrators and defenders
And a country of bystanders
No way, things like that
This can't be everything about Korea
part of this land
It's just that they're effectively controlling it.
Here's Kaya
In such a barbaric country
Because I was persecuted
Before
The only legitimate government in the land
To a free and just Republic of Korea
is applying for asylum
Your Honor’s Republic of Korea
Which one?
Your honor
belonging to the judiciary of a country
Are you a judge?
Plaintiff's representative!
I'll take a short break.
agent for both sides
Please come to my room for a moment
everyone in their seats
Please stand up
- I'll go in.
- Ha…
Hmm
Judge David Kang!
I'm a lawyer now, your honor.
Still, the person who was once a judge
What is this doing?
I am just patriotic
I am a person who has worked in public office all my life.
Now with honor
Just the day I retire
I'm waiting
To this clown
Are you going to make me a bridesmaid?
Are you saying you're a clown?
Oh well, of course
I may be a clown, but
This trial is not a farce
It's a fight
desperate
Ha…
Your honor?
This
Is this a trial you are trying to win?
just in public
To disgrace the country
Isn't it a trial?
They invited a bunch of reporters to the front row.
At the end of every word
‘Republic of Korea’, ‘Republic of Korea’!
By exposing my country’s shame
What do you want to do?
Judge Kang
Don't you have the slightest sense of patriotism?
That person was originally
To win
This is a person who does anything
Such a ridiculous trial...
Let's get it over with right away, your honor.
Um…
I am
Because I believe in my country, Korea
This trial has begun
Baby, you don't even give me a chance to fight
If you end it right away
Maybe I'm scared and running away
Can I think about it?
A Marine who catches ghosts
Your honor?
Oh, no way
What's wrong, what's wrong!
Come here
Come out here!
kid…
Are you okay?
Manager Jo Kang-yeol is very hot-tempered.
You're famous for being a jerk.
By any chance, what
Well, I got kicked somewhere.
Isn't it true?
Oh, then thank you to me
Lie down right now
File a lawsuit claiming compensation from the state
I need to hit the live broadcast.
kid, that
I'm really glad that the trial went ahead.
Oh, is it okay?
Ah, Attorney Kang’s argument.
I also 100% agree with you in my heart.
Legally...
Of course
Of course we lose
Yes? Why do you know?
Even though I knew I would lose
I heard there are trials that need to be done.
Wow, that
I heard that’s what public defenders do?
Oh no
That, ‘even lawsuits are difficult to win’
‘If we fight and create a precedent’
‘Someday, you may change the world’
That's the story
Ms. Kaya right now...
I want to change the world
I'm not interested
right now
Except I won my case.
No, of course you're going to lose?
Even if you lose the trial, you win the case.
at least
time is on our side
What does that mean?
There's a month and a half left now, right?
world refugee day
Huh?
Ugh
world refugee day
President Choi Young-seop
Historic UN plenary session speech
It's coming
Huh?
her!
president
UN speech
The reporter I know is a reporter.
We gathered everyone together
Internet articles will be pouring in by now.
The Ministry of Justice, the responsible ministry,
You'll be shocked
Hey, the president
Because I'm going to go all the way to the UN and be humiliated.
I think I'll make a deal.
The key point of this trial is
Are you making noise in the world?
So that you can't pretend not to know
Ah…
You understand quickly, Attorney Park.
Now, everyone remembers, right?
Attorney Park's favorite
courtroom movies
Last scene?
yes? What is that?
Hmm, hmm
Now
From now on, I will call you by name.
David Kang Attorney
yes
Let's go out first.
Yes?
Attorney Youngsil Jang
Yes, I will go out and try it too.
Where, where are you going?
Where are you going, where are you going!
Attorney Junwoo Hwang
What?
I'm taking good care of my office.
Uh, that…
No, that's not it...
Joy, where are you going?
What kind of movie is that!
Everyone, please take your seats.
Oh, what's going on?
These lawyers
Why are so many gathered here?
That one side
What's going on?
Your honor
Public Interest Human Rights Law Foundation
These are lawyers from Donggam.
We are
I agree with the purpose of this lawsuit.
Joined as a joint agent
We are
They are lawyers widely incorporated in the corporation.
We too
As a joint representative
We want to be together
Gyeongcheon Foundation
These are lawyers, your honor.
Now in this audience
So far, we have represented
Clients are here
who persecuted the plaintiff Kaya
from that very country
These are the people who have been harmed.
Let these people have their say for a moment.
May I make a request?
Please tell me
I am a victim of dating violence
I mustered up the courage to report it, but
They say it's a relationship between lovers.
The police forced an agreement
I am a victim of sexual harassment at work
The perpetrator, who is a superior,
I got drunk and left, saying it was a mistake.
I'm the only one who raised the issue
I was fired
I am
I am a victim of child sexual abuse
That hellish memory
It's still vivid
The beast is already on the loose
I moved to the town next to me
Is this a country?
Besides these people
A lot of people
Just like Kaya
From that barbaric country
You have suffered damage
Our representatives also
I feel the same way
ignoring the victims
A country that shelters perpetrators
In such a country
no more
I don't want to live
Dear Judge,
All of us here now
Please accept my asylum application
Please accept it!
under…
public avengers
It's scary.
If it's a fight, they're the ones who win.
Okay, now that I know,
Everyone please sit down.
Plaintiff Representative
Please continue
Your honor
refugee claimants
It's not just these people
Please accept my asylum application!
apply for asylum
This shit
I want to leave the country!
apply for asylum
no
So much so that they call themselves refugees.
People who are angry
Are there this many?
Your Honor, now the plaintiff
By bringing in external forces
Trying to court public opinion
Because of one foreign woman
What kind of mess is this?
This trial
Harmful to the national interests of the Republic of Korea
It's a trial that disgraces the country...
One foreign woman?
Isn't it?
The defendant's attorney said the case is still
Does it seem like someone else’s business?
This incident
Not only Kaya
Anyone can experience this
universal women's human rights
It's a trampled incident.
Are you saying it harms the national interests of the Republic of Korea?
Let's look at the pictures.
working in a factory
foreign worker
working in the rice fields
foreign daughter-in-law
people left and left
our rice fields
Those who came from far away
I keep it like this
Your honor
fact
Considering nationality
So meaningless
It's a global world
Wow, today
Lawyers from large law firms
They came out in large numbers.
Attorney Woo
All of your children
Are you a US citizen?
Uh, congratulations.
Every time I go to New York to give birth,
Thank you for your hard work
Attorney Jeong
Recently Dominican nationality
You acquired it?
I heard there is no tax there.
Huh, really…
Attorney Pyo, Attorney Joo
Since your children are in kindergarten
While attending a foreign school
You went to study abroad, right?
The two of you too
Are you preparing to immigrate?
What are you doing now?
Plaintiff's representative!
I am very curious
In New York and LA
Born in an expedition birth
In Korea
Coming to visit for a short vacation
with black haired foreigners
Koreans ignore
Protecting rural areas, fishing villages, and factories
I'm learning Korean hard
Among Koreans who came from far away
Who are the members of this society?
This trial earlier
It's a disgrace to the country
You said it would harm national interests.
That national interest is
For whom is the national interest?
Your honor
The Republic of Korea
Who lives in Korea?
us now
What country do you live in?
Have you finished arguing? Plaintiff Representative
Yes, that's it, your honor.
this incident
Argument concluded
The verdict will be announced in two weeks.
That national interest is
For whom is the national interest?
under…
Your honor
The Republic of Korea
Who lives in Korea?
Everyone, please take your seats.
Before the sentencing
I thought about many things
Honestly, legally,
I took on a ridiculous case
After 35 years of my judicial career,
This is my first time
The plaintiff's attorney asked me, right?
Which side of Korea is your country?
Do you belong to the judiciary of any country?
Are you a judge?
It's personal
Honestly, I'm sorry and embarrassed, but
Even though I passed the exam
I volunteered to join the Marine Corps.
I worked as a general soldier
Make me proud for the rest of my life
I am a person who has lived
my grandfather
From Manchuria to the Independence Army
He died fighting against Japanese colonial rule.
my father
Protesting against dictatorship during 4.19
He died after fighting on the street.
Throughout this trial
I thought about it carefully.
3 generations of our family
This Republic of Korea, which we have risked our lives to protect,
What kind of country is it?
No matter how much I think about it
One thing is certain
chase your dreams
came to this land from far away
To that young man
I will be cruel, shamelessly
Such a backward country that pushes out and persecutes
This is not my Korea
perpetrators and defenders
Not a country of bystanders
The only legitimate government in the land
To a free and just Republic of Korea
You said you were applying for asylum, right?
No matter how much I think about it
For the past 35 years I
That just and free
As a judge in Korea
Looks like I've been working
No way…
Oh my...
I pronounce judgment
The defendant
Regarding the manuscript
Refugee non-recognition
cancel
- Yes!
- Mmm!
The cost of litigation is
Defendant pays
Yes!
Um, your honor...
everyone in their seats
Please stand up
Your honor!
Mr. Kaya
Yes, your honor.
It's been hard all this time, right?
I'm sorry
And thank you
For coming to Korea
Hey!
and!
historic world refugee day
It arose ahead of the UN speech
In the aftermath of the so-called asylum ruling
The Blue House is in trouble.
First of all, we
a special position
It's not a matter to bring up
I think so
On the human rights situation in Korea
questioning
-There are a series of foreign media reports.
- It became a hot topic
our trial article
The comment window was very upset.
- Hahaha
- Wow!
‘I am applying for asylum’
How many hashtags are there?
Good, good
It's going according to plan
The Ministry of Justice must be very upset.
I will appeal, but
I'll make a deal in a few minutes.
us
Let's finish it quickly!
- Yes
- Attorney Kang
Uh, why, yellow stool?
What's wrong with your expression?
I did it the other day
Kaya, take off your body and wear pants.
The thing that squeaks
Have so much fun
My rice, Byeolstar
Oh, you posted it?
her!
Anyway, you have unique tastes
But why?
But that
Who is his star?
Do you know if it was uploaded?
why…
Wow, it's frustrating
Who did what?
- Get something, huh?
- Uh, what's going on?
'black'
‘Pink Jenny’?
Blackpink Jennie?
- Wow, ah...
- evil!
- Huh, huh, uh!
-What, what…
- her! Nanhee
- Uh, huh? Argh!
- Ugh!
- under…
- hey…
- haha…
Je, Jenny…
Me, Attorney Kang
refugee case
please withdraw
Our Ministry of Justice
It turned upside down
What are you talking about?
Whoever takes it should do it.
Withdraw the appeal
Have you seen this yet?
Now, Gukbbong YouTubers
It's so crazy
No, Korea
Thanks to your contribution to informing the world
Even giving a medal is not enough
Are you appealing the first trial ruling?
Uh, what to do
How are you doing this?
Please just withdraw the complaint.
Kaya's problem
We will take responsibility
What and how do you take responsibility?
Yes, I mean
So that there are no problems during your stay in Korea.
Give me a work visa
We will also provide settlement support funds.
Well, if you want, we can give you a job too...
I want
Ah, then, I
I thought you were withdrawing the lawsuit.
Is it okay if I go?
Oh, go ahead.
Okay, now
Shall we go and fight the rest?
Kaya's father-in-law's second trial
I need to send you back to jail.
For a long time
Umm
Not so much there
You don't have to worry about it.
Why?
I met the grim reaper, that father-in-law.
The grim reaper?
I lost my mind for a moment
I just made a mistake when I was drunk.
They say criminals pray?
‘Only Judge Jeong Eui-hyeon, the Grim Reaper.
Please let me avoid it'
So who is going to sin?
Shameless guys
Well, in the first trial
200 hours of community service
that's too much
I would like to say this
Oh, and finally
"buy porridge"
to the extent permitted by law
The judge's wise judgment
Looking forward to it…
“Advisor Oh Gyu-jang”
uh
Are you here, my daughter?
Did you call me, father?
Yeah
sit, sit
yes
Ah…
You too
Did you see this?
This was very fun, right? Yeah
Since Judge Kang came
There's no time to be bored
father
Father now too
Put down your work and
Do some hobbies too.
Ride the bike you mentioned back then.
Oh, and you also play electric guitar…
Jeong In-ah
Dad is
Power is my hobby
Bike, guitar?
Something like that
Only small citizens enjoy it.
oh my god
There is nothing more fun than power
If you also took the position of representative
Do you really need to know that much?
I'm working hard
Don't let your father's reputation be tarnished
Working hard isn't enough
You have to do well
Disband, Pro Bono Team.
Yes?
father
Hello~
- Are you here?
- hi
- Hello~
More and more I
I think I'm getting healthier.
Lawyer, really.
Ah~
That health checkup at that time
Hey, Attorney Kang.
I have this again
He's a guy who isn't scared of anything.
But I'm the only one
Well, there is an injection needle.
Well, I have a phobia of needles.
That day over there, he was getting an injection...
Look
You don't hear it
Anesthesia~
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hold on tight, hold on tight
Okay!
Ouch! Wow
Surprise, surprise, surprise
What, what, what?
I'm not guilty
What is it?
Lawyer Kang is not guilty, not guilty!
yes?
A video of me receiving a bribe
Judge fired due to threats
- You're here.
- They say they're all fired!
From Attorney Kang
O&Partners sales
Following closely
Baekseung Law Firm
Stick with it
What if they steal the client?
The meeting is scheduled for today.
There's one thing you can do, so try to do it well
Evil! no
How did Mr. Elijah get here…?
I heard you were crushed during the first meeting?
- I'm not going to destroy it.
- This time we will do it at EK Entertainment.
Baek Seung and Competitive PT
We will protect you
Mr. Elijah
This video has been uploaded
What?
Research into the client's industry
Was it not enough?
I don't know